

Gustavo Yunier Leyte-Vidal Chacón

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

✓ glcdmx@gmail.com

+5356274921

💡 Havana, Cuba

MY LINKS

gustavoylc

y gustavoylc

in gustavoylc

mnf.red/gustavoylc

Languages

Spanish



English



Introduction

I am a Frontend Developer with more than 9 years of experience in the field. I have a passion for web development. I'm always up for a challenge and eager to learn more. I would love to collaborate in a high-impact project to enhance my professional knowledge.

My skills



Adaptability to change



Continuous learning



Ability to receive feedback

Technologies and tools

I MASTER

CSS / HTML / Figma / Tailwind / TypeScript / MaterialUI / Sass / Postman / React / NextJS / Git / JavaScript / Jest

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE/CAREER



Front10

Frontend Developer
 Feb 2023 — TODAY (2 months)

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / React / NextJS



Fullstack Developer at Documentary Heritage

Dec 2013 — Sep 2021 (7 yrs. and 10 months)

- Application for the control of temperature and relative humidity with digital thermo-hygrometers for decision making, generating different statistics according to behavior (FrontEnd)
- Development of a small application for the control of basic means of the company (Backend)

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

Laravel / JavaScript / Vue / API

EDUCATION/**DEGREES**

Degrees



UCI

University of Informatic Sciences
 Sep 2007 — Jul 2012 (4 yrs. and 11 months)

Certificates



EF SET English Certificate 46/100 (B1 Intermediate)

Issued by: EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

Jan 2023 — TODAY (3 months)



Platzi learning platform

Issued by: Platzi

Mar 2021 — TODAY (2 yrs. and 1 month)



BUT WAIT...

THERE'S EVEN MORE IN MY PROFILE.

This is a short version of my Profile, but a longer one is available where you can see more interesting and relevant data.

+ Click here or scan the QR code